individualhealthquotes.com 2014-06-20

# Individual Health Quotes Privacy Policy - Any Quote. Anytime.

This website is owned and operated by the IndividualHealthQuotes network. IndividualHealthQuotes is a leading online source of information for people seeking to learn more about their insurance options. IndividualHealthQuotes also matches people in need of insurance services with insurance professionals who can provide those services. The use of our matching service (hereinafter "Service" or "Services") is free for consumers.

IndividualHealthQuotes believes it is important for you to know and understand how websites collect and use your information, and the steps we take we to protect your privacy. Please read this privacy policy carefully.

Please note that this privacy policy only applies to this website. Other websites in the IndividualHealthQuotes network may have different privacy policies.

By accessing this website and/or using our Service, you agree to abide by this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.

### Services Offered By IndividualHealthQuotes

IndividualHealthQuotes works with a nationwide network of insurance professionals. When you use our Service, we will attempt to match you with professionals who are qualified to provide you with the insurance information you have expressed interest in. The professionals you are matched with may contact you with information and offers for the services you have expressed interest in. Please note that you have no obligation to accept any offer.

IndividualHealthQuotes is not an insurance agency. We are solely a referral service for connecting consumers with qualified professionals.

### Information Collected By IndividualHealthQuotes

IndividualHealthQuotes uses this website to collect two (2) kinds of information: **personally-identifiable information** and **non-personally-identifiable information**.

**Personally-identifiable information:**

When you use our Service you are authorizing the sharing of your inquiry and your personal information with other businesses who provide services that match your inquiry. The personal information we collect may include, but is not limited to:

  * Name
  * Address
  * Email address
  * Phone number
  * Demographic information
  * Credit information 
  * Health information
  * Other financial information

Please note that insurance institutions and other services who subscribe to our system compete for the opportunity to provide insurance products and services that match your inquiry. By submitting your information to us, you are also authorizing these businesses to contact you directly by e-mail and telephone with information about insurance products or services they offer that match your inquiry. You expressly consent to receive phone calls and email regardless of whether you are on any Federal or state DNC (“Do Not Call”) and/or DNE (“Do Not Email”) list or registry.

**Non-personally-identifiable information:**

While you are visiting this website, our hosting service will automatically track information that may include:

  * IP addresses
  * Referral information 
  * Browser details 
  * Number of page views
  * Number of repeat visits
  * Internet Service Provider
  * Region or geographic location

### How Information Is Collected

**Personally-identifiable information:**  
We only collect your personally-identifiable information when you choose to share it with us. We will not collect any personally-identifiable information without your consent. 

The information you choose to share with us may be collected through this website, another website in the IndividualHealthQuotes network, or a website owned by of one of our third-party partners. Information may also be collected over the phone by one of our Customer Service Representative, or by a Customer Service Representative working for one of our third-party partners.

By agreeing to the Terms of Use of this privacy policy, you are consenting to share your information you supply to us, and, you are authorizing the sharing of your inquiry information and your personal information with other businesses that provide insurance products or services that match your inquiry. By submitting your information to us, you are also authorizing these businesses to contact you directly by e-mail and telephone with information about insurance products or services they offer that match your inquiry, as well as other services and offers you may be interested in. 

**Non-personally-identifiable information:**  
While you are visiting this website, at least, the following information will be automatically tracked: IP addresses, referral information, browser details, operating system information, information about your Internet Service Provider, geographic location, and other non-personally-identifiable information. We may use cookies, web beacons/pixels, tracking scripts, and other monitoring technologies to gather non-personally-identifiable information. 

### How Information Is Used

**Personally-identifiable information:**

          **Consumers:**  
If you choose to give us personally-identifiable information, we may share this information with our network of insurance professionals to help answer your questions or fulfill your request, as well as other third parties. The professionals we match you with may contact you by phone, email, or mail to fulfill your inquiry and provide you with other offers you may be interested in.

The professionals in our network may include, but are not limited to, insurance agents, discount program representatives, and other financial services brokers. 

In addition, you may be contacted by IndividualHealthQuotes's Consumer Protection or Quality Assurance departments in order to verify information you submitted or to collect additional information from you about your experience using our Service.

You should be aware that we have no control over how other businesses with which we share your information, may use it, or whether they will sell or share your information with third parties. Consequently, these businesses may have direct access to your information. 

If you choose to send us an email, we may forward your request on to third parties if we cannot answer your question. We may also respond to your email with correspondence or offers which we believe may be relevant to your request.

In addition, we may provide you with a free subscription to one of our newsletters. You may unsubscribe to these newsletters and any other correspondence or offer from IndividualHealthQuotes at any time.

In the event that we cannot match you with a member of our network of insurance professionals, your information may be shared with other third-party networks of professionals. Any contact or communication you have with members of these third-party networks is not covered by the terms of this privacy policy. 

Please note that we have no control over and cannot be held responsible or liable for the privacy policies, if any, of our third-party partners. This includes third-party websites that link to IndividualHealthQuotes, third-party websites linked from IndividualHealthQuotes, any insurance agent or financial professional in our network that we match you with, any third-party network to whom we forward your information, or any member of such third-party network.

Finally, your agreement with our privacy policy also allows that we may share your information with All Inbox, LLC only for purposes of providing you via email with special offers or services in which you may be interested from IndividualHealthQuote-email.com or other third parties as we determine at our sole discretion. You may unsubscribe at any time.

We reserve the right to use the data you choose to share with us for any legally permissible purpose. 

**Prospective business partners and affiliates:**  
The information you submit to IndividualHealthQuotes's affiliate and/or referral program may be used to qualify you for participation in affiliate and/or referral programs. 

**Non-personally-identifiable information:**  
Our website development team uses non-personally-identifiable metrics to improve the content, layout, navigation, and overall site experience for all visitors. We may analyze traffic patterns and statistics to improve this site, provide additional services,  and better serve our visitors.

### Your Consent

By visiting, agreeing with and accepting this privacy policy, and then sharing your information with this website, you consent to the collection and use of your information by our site development team. In so doing, you agree to abide by this Privacy Policy, this site's Terms of Use, and this site's disclaimer.

You further acknowledge that this website's Privacy Policy and Terms of Use constitute the only understanding and agreement between you and IndividualHealthQuotes, and that this understanding and agreement supersedes any and all previous understandings and agreements. 

You further acknowledge that you agree to be contacted by insurance professionals, the IndividualHealthQuotes Consumer Protection and/or Quality Assurance departments, and other third party partners of IndividualHealthQuotes, regardless of the presence of your telephone number on any state or Federal DNC (“Do Not Call”) of DNE (“Do Not Email”) list or registry.

You further agree to receive quotes, policy updates, and other customized content to your wireless phone. In addition to any fee of which you are notified, your provider's standard messaging rates apply to our confirmation and all subsequent SMS correspondence. GoHealth does not charge you for sending or receiving text messages. You may opt-out and remove your SMS information by sending "STOP", "END", "QUIT" to the SMS text message you have received.

### California Residents Privacy Rights 

Companies that collect personally-identifiable information from California residents and disclose such information to Third Parties (including affiliated entities) for marketing purposes must, in response to a request by a consumer, either (1) provide a list detailing the categories of information shared and the entities to which such information was provided, or (2) provide a mechanism by which a consumer may opt-out of having their information shared with Third Parties.

IndividualHealthQuotes has elected the second option, and you may request that your personally-identifiable information not be shared with third parties by sending your request, including your full name, email address and postal address to:

IndividualHealthQuotes  
40 E. Chicago Avenue  
Suite 176  
Chicago, IL 60611

In accordance with California Civil Code Sec. 1789.3, California resident users are entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R Street, Suite 1080, Sacramento, CA 95814; or by phone at 916-445-1254 or 800-952-5210; or by email to dca@dca.ca.gov.

### CAN-SPAM Compliance

IndividualHealthQuotes is committed to be compliant with all Federal regulations, including the Federal CAN-SPAM Act of 2003.

IndividualHealthQuotes only sends email to those of our visitors who have “opted in” to receive these communications. Individuals “opt in” to our email communications by voluntarily providing us with their email address and submitting a form that acknowledges their agreement with our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.

You may “opt-out” of any communication from IndividualHealthQuotes at any time. Use the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any email you receive from IndividualHealthQuotes, and we will remove you from our mailing list. In addition, you may contact us at the address above and request to be removed from our mailing list.

Occasionally IndividualHealthQuotes.com will partner with a third party email server who may provide additional relevant email advertisements to our consumer’s requests.

Unsubscribing from communications from IndividualHealthQuotes does not guarantee that you will no longer receive communications from our third party partners.

Be advised that we cannot control the policies of our third party partners, nor can we guarantee or represent their compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act or any other state or Federal law. 

### Links to Other Websites

This website may feature links to other websites owned and operated by third parties. Be advised that IndividualHealthQuotes is not responsible for the content or services of these third party sites. Privacy Policies and Terms of Use, if any, of these third party sites may differ from IndividualHealthQuotes's Privacy Policy and Terms of Use. We encourage you to read the Privacy Policies and Terms of Use of any website you visit.

### Information from Minors

IndividualHealthQuotes does not knowingly solicit or collect information from anyone under the age of 13.

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about IndividualHealthQuotes, this website, our service, or this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at:

IndividualHealthQuotes  
220 W. Huron  
Chicago, IL 60654

1-888-250-2309

### Changes to This Policy

IndividualHealthQuotes reserves the right to make changes and updates to this Privacy Policy at any time. It is your sole responsibility to remain aware of any such changes. In the event that there is a change to this privacy policy, such updates will be immediately reflected on this page. An updated copy of this Privacy Policy will be clearly posted and accessible on this website at all times.

Last updated: January 19, 2012
